# Ijlal Ahmad

### Full Stack Android/Web Developer

I am a Full Stack Android and Web Developer, have made many production ready applications and been in programming world for almost 7 years. Worked for many companies in contracts and internship basis. I am a tech enthusiast and loves to read books and watching movies in my free time.



ijlalahmad845@gmail.com



8279789236



Sambhal, India



linkedin.com/in/ijlal-ahmad-14aa35202



github.com/thre4dripper



instagram.com/thre4dripper

### **SKILLS**

Android

React

React Native

Node

Firebase

MySQL

MongoDb

Cloud

Docker

. . . . . . . . . . . .

Git

Githu

DSA

TypeScript

Java

Kotlin

C/C++

### **LANGUAGES**

#### English

Professional Working Proficiency

Hindi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

### **INTERESTS**

**Books and Movies** 

Science and Tech

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Bea Brand

02/2023 - Present

India

Working as a Backend Developer Intern on Nodejs (Typescript) in ecommerce based company, One stop solution platform for your Fashion Brand

# **Android Developer Intern** Trakkia, Yantrasksh

12/2022 - 05/2023 India

Worked as Lead Android Developer on a IOT based warehouse RFID scanning project that can be linked to any android device and scan loads of products in seconds.

# **Software Developer Intern** SOPAY

10/2022 - 01/2023 India

Full-stack developer - Worked on the react-native-based app as well as new feature flags and bug resolution

## Android Developer

Meta16 Labs

01/2023 - 01/2023 India

Helped M16 Labs implement core android features in their one of the flagship project.

### **CERTIFICATES AND ACHIEVEMENTS**

Smart India Hackathon 2022 Finalist (07/2022 - 08/2022)

I with a team of six are the finalists of Smart India Hackathon 2022.

30 Days of Google Cloud Challenge (07/2021 - 08/2021)

This challenge is from Google Qwikabs, I have completed Google Cloud Engineering Tracks about DevOps

### PERSONAL PROJECTS

Graphical Password Authentication (08/2022 - 09/2022)

 Smart India Hackathon Project, Authentication system based on Grids of Images that solved many problems with Text based password systems.

Exam Portal (10/2022 - 11/2022)

 An exam portal for Singapore-based school, Ability to upload and conduct tests and give results asap with analytics and all required customizations.

Discussions Social Media App (10/2022 - 12/2023)

 A fully featured social media like discussions app with best industry practices and architectural patterns, and scalable backend.

PM Health Care Android App (09/2021 - 10/2021)

M Health Care Android App (09/2021 - 10/2021) This App was based on PM Health Care Digital Mission, in which each citizen will be given a unique health Id (Phone number) and he/she can store their medical documents and all previous medical records on cloud (Firebase).

### **EDUCATION**

B. Tech. (C.S.E.) Jamia Millia Islamia

10/2020 - Present New Delhi, India

Intermediate (XII), Science Bal Vidya Mandir Sr. Sec. School, Sambhal

04/2016 - 04/2018 Distt. Sambhal, U.P., India